A Guide to the Policy Office Legislative Files of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2001
Library of Virginia
- SB 366 (00) Self-service storage facilities; liens (Box 25, Folder 102)
- SB 367 (00) Public building authorities; powers (Box 25, Folder 103)
- SB 368 (00) College building authority (Box 25, Folder 104)
- SB 369 (00) Labor and employment polygraphs (Box 25, Folder 105)
- SB 370 (00) Court of appeals; judges (Box 25, Folder 106)
- SB 372 (00) Computer information transactions act (Box 25, Folder 107)
- SB 373 (00) Tuition grants for certain students (Box 25, Folder 108)
- SB 374 (00) Enterprise zone act (Box 25, Folder 109)
- SB 375 (00) Parcel identification numbers; use of land record cover sheets (Box 25, Folder 110)
- SB 376 (00) Nonprofit debt counseling agencies; fees and qualifications (Box 25, Folder 111)
- SB 377 (00) Commercial vehicles; use of certain lanes on highways prohibited (Box 25, Folder 112)
- SB 380 (00) Child day programs exempt from licensure (Box 25, Folder 113)
- SB 381 (00) Board of equalization; notice of sittings (Box 25, Folder 114)
- SB 382 (00) Presidential primaries; age qualification to participate (Box 25, Folder 115)
- SB 383 (00) Public procurement act; exemptions (Box 25, Folder 116)
- SB 384 (00) Civil remedies; medical malpractice (Box 25, Folder 117)
- SB 385 (00) Civil procedure; audio-visual depositions (Box 25, Folder 118)
- SB 386 (00) Health professions; exemption from licensure (Box 26, Folder 1)
- SB 388 (00) Administration of the State Workers' Compensation Program (Box 26, Folder 2)
- SB 389 (00) Resources authority; Board of Directors (Box 26, Folder 3)
- SB 390 (00) FOIA; vehicle identification data (Box 26, Folder 4)
- SB 391 (00) Board for Barbers and Cosmetology (Box 26, Folder 5)
- SB 392 (00) Voter registration system and collection of moneys (Box 26, Folder 6)
- SB 395 (00) Sale of artificially raised trout (Box 26, Folder 7)
- SB 396 (00) Protection of farm and forest lands (Box 26, Folder 8)
- SB 398 (00) Marriage licenses not returned by minister (Box 26, Folder 9)
- SB 399 (00) Prisons and other methods of corrections (Box 26, Folder 10)
- SB 400 (00) Duties of the Department for the Aging (Box 26, Folder 11)
- SB 401 (00) Annual reports by guardians (Box 26, Folder 12)
- SB 403 (00) Powers of cooperatives (Box 26, Folder 13)
- SB 404 (00) Motor vehicle security interests (Box 26, Folder 14)
- SB 405 (00) Tort liability; hospitals (Box 26, Folder 15)
- SB 406 (00) Peninsula Port Authority of Virginia (Box 26, Folder 16)
- SB 407 (00) Motor vehicle dealers; hearings before DMV Commissioner (Box 26, Folder 17)
- SB 409 (00) Adoption of ordinances and resolutions (Box 26, Folder 18)
- SB 411 (00) Charter schools (Box 26, Folder 19)
- SB 413 (00) Special license plates; supporters of public schools; fees (Box 26, Folder 20)
- SB 414 (00) "Photo red" traffic light signal enforcement program (Box 26, Folder 21)
- SB 415 (00) Health insurance and retirement benefits; surviving spouses of persons killed (Box 26, Folder 22)
- SB 417 (00) Campaign finance disclosure act (Box 26, Folder 23)
- SB 418 (00) Candidates in presidential and referenda elections (Box 26, Folder 24)
- SB 420 (00) Voter registration; transfers and cancellations (Box 26, Folder 25)
- SB 421 (00) Tax credits; coalfield employment enhancement tax credit (Box 26, Folder 26)
- SB 423 (00) Southwest Virginia Higher Education Center (Box 26, Folder 27)
- SB 429 (00) Elections; voting machines and equipment (Box 26, Folder 28)
- SB 430 (00) Elections; activities at polling places; election pages (Box 26, Folder 29)
- SB 432 (00) Running for multiple offices; names on ballots (Box 26, Folder 30)
- SB 434 (00) Health professions; data required (Box 26, Folder 31)
- SB 437 (00) Preschool physical examinations (Box 26, Folder 32)
- SB 438 (00) Student representatives on boards of visitors (Box 26, Folder 33)
- SB 440 (00) Local animal ordinances (Box 26, Folder 34)
- SB 441 (00) Department of Personnel and Training name change to Department of Human Resource Management (Box 26, Folder 35)
- SB 442 (00) Child support; dental coverage (Box 26, Folder 36)
- SB 445 (00) Public utilities; underground utility line separation standards (Box 26, Folder 37)
- SB 446 (00) Termination of parental rights (Box 26, Folder 38)
- SB 447 (00) Foster care (Box 26, Folder 39)
- SB 452 (00) Transportation Commissioner; eminent domain (Box 26, Folder 40)
- SB 453 (00) Eminent domain procedures (Box 26, Folder 41)
- SB 454 (00) Public broadcasting board; definitions (Box 26, Folder 42)
- SB 455 (00) Health insurance for small employers; bona fide associations (Box 26, Folder 43)
- SB 456 (00) Cancellation of insurance policies (Box 26, Folder 44)
- SB 457 (00) ABC; compensation of employees (Box 26, Folder 45)
- SB 458 (00) Location of highway routes (Box 26, Folder 46)
- SB 459 (00) Rappahannock River Basin Commission (Box 26, Folder 47)
- SB 460 (00) Institutes for training teachers, administrators and librarians (Box 26, Folder 48)
- SB 461 (00) Improper driving (Box 26, Folder 49)
- SB 474 (00) Parking in Fairfax County (Box 26, Folder 50)
- SB 479 (00) Division of risk management (Box 26, Folder 51)
- SB 481 (00) Compensation of court appointed counsel (Box 26, Folder 52)
- SB 483 (00) Special tax district in counties containing a town school division (Box 26, Folder 53)
- SB 484 (00) Health research fund (Box 26, Folder 54)
- SB 485 (00) Ballots and voting equipment (Box 26, Folder 55)
- SB 487 (00) Standards of quality; gender-diverse and disabled persons (Box 26, Folder 56)
- SB 488 (00) Nursing workforce information (Box 26, Folder 57)
- SB 489 (00) Health workforce recruitment and retention; study report (Box 26, Folder 58)
- SB 490 (00) Statewide asthma management (Box 26, Folder 59)
- SB 494 (00) Health professions; occupational therapists (Box 26, Folder 60)
- SB 495 (00) Income tax; military retirement pay of holders of medal of honor (Box 26)
- SB 498 (00) Fire prevention code; enforcement by locality (Box 26, Folder 62)
- SB 499 (00) Admission to public schools for certain students; tuition charges (Box 26, Folder 63)
- SB 502 (00) Rule against perpetuities (Box 26, Folder 64)
- SB 505 (00) State Lottery fund; profits (Box 26, Folder 65)
- SB 506 (00) Temporary assistance to needy families (TANF) benefits and services (Box 26, Folder 66)
- SB 510 (00) Unlicensed child day centers; staff rations (Box 26, Folder 67)
- SB 514 (00) Boiler and pressure vessel safety act injunctions (Box 26, Folder 68)
- SB 515 (00) Health; Medicaid forecasting (Box 26, Folder 69)
- SB 517 (00) Health insurance; long-term care insurance for local employees (Box 26, Folder 70)
- SB 518 (00) Grant program for respite care services (Box 26, Folder 71)
- SB 519 (00) Department for the aging toll free hotline (Box 26, Folder 72)
- SB 520 (00) Juvenile competency (Box 26, Folder 73)
- SB 522 (00) Outdoor advertising (Box 26, Folder 74)
- SB 523 (00) Alcoholic beverage control; refusal to grant license (Box 26, Folder 75)
- SB 524 (00) Who may be present for execution of search warrants (Box 26, Folder 76)
- SB 525 (00) Driving while intoxicated (Box 26, Folder 77)
- SB 529 (00) Certain health professional credentials (Box 26, Folder 78)
- SB 530 (00) Fuels tax; tax at the rack (Box 26, Folder 79)
- SB 531 (00) Landscape architecture (Box 26, Folder 80)
- SB 532 (00) Electric utility restructuring; capped rates (Box 26, Folder 81)
- SB 533 (00) Health care data reporting (Box 26, Folder 82)
- SB 534 (00) Pest law (Box 26, Folder 83)
- SB 535 (00) Ignition interlock system (Box 26, Folder 84)
- SB 537 (00) Estimated tax payments; estates and trusts (Box 26, Folder 85)
- SB 538 (00) Procurement Act; multiple awards (Box 26, Folder 86)
- SB 541 (00) Accident and sickness insurance; coverage for morbid obesity (Box 26, Folder 87)
- SB 542 (00) Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation (Box 26, Folder 88)
- SB 545 (00) Extended school year incentive program (Box 26, Folder 89)
- SB 546 (00) Constitutional amendment (voter referendum); lottery proceeds fund (Box 26, Folder 90)
- SB 548 (00) Action for test security violations (Box 26, Folder 91)
- SB 550 (00) Health insurance for children (Box 26, Folder 92)
- SB 551 (00) Organ and tissue donor registry (Box 26, Folder 93)
- SB 552 (00) Persons with mental retardation, developmental disabilities, etc. (Box 26, Folder 94)
- SB 554 (00) Persons with mental retardation, developmental disabilities, etc. (Box 26, Folder 95)
- SB 555 (00) Persons with mental retardation, developmental disabilities, etc. (Box 26, Folder 96)
- SB 558 (00) Local taxes; payment of administrative costs, etc. (Box 26, Folder 97)
- SB 559 (00) Tuition assistance grants (Box 26, Folder 98)
- SB 562 (00) Hobby and model boilers' inspection and testing (Box 26, Folder 99)
- SB 563 (00) Southeastern public service authority of Virginia (Box 26, Folder 100)
- SB 564 (00) Long-term care nursing scholarship and loan repayment program (Box 26, Folder 101)
- SB 565 (00) Practitioner self-referral act (Box 26, Folder 102)
- SB 567 (00) Local fire marshals; police powers (Box 26, Folder 103)
- SB 568 (00) Biotechnology research park authority, powers and duties (Box 26, Folder 104)
- SB 575 (00) Statewide cancer registry; civil penalties (Box 26, Folder 105)
- SB 576 (00) Dentist loan repayment program (Box 27, Folder 1)
- SB 577 (00) Adult care residences; training (Box 27, Folder 2)
- SB 578 (00) Vehicle safety inspections (Box 27, Folder 3)
- SB 579 (00) State employees; defense of such persons (Box 27, Folder 4)
- SB 580 (00) Town of Altavista; election of council (Box 27)
- SB 581 (00) Tobacco settlement foundation and tobacco indemnification and community revitalization commission (Box 27, Folder 6)
- SB 582 (00) Motor fuels; direct fueling of commercial vehicles (Box 27, Folder 7)
- SB 583 (00) Joint commission on workforce development (Box 27, Folder 8)
- SB 584 (00) Disposition of surplus materials (Box 27, Folder 9)
- SB 585 (00) Electric utility restructuring (Box 27, Folder 10)
- SB 587 (00) Insurance rate and form regulation; exempting large commercial risks (Box 27, Folder 11)
- SB 589 (00) School resource officers (Box 27, Folder 12)
- SB 590 (00) Child visitation (Box 27, Folder 13)
- SB 591 (00) Alcoholic beverage control; farm wineries (Box 27, Folder 14)
- SB 592 (00) Economic development partnership; Virginia tourism authority (Box 27, Folder 15)
- SB 593 (00) Dental and optometric insurance (Box 27, Folder 16)
- SB 594 (00) Utility consumer services cooperatives (Box 27, Folder 17)
- SB 595 (00) Correctional impact statements (Box 27, Folder 18)
- SB 596 (00) Certificate of public need (Box 27, Folder 19)
- SB 597 (00) Circuit court fees (Box 27, Folder 20)
- SB 598 (00) Live horseracing compact (Box 27, Folder 21)
- SB 599 (00) Racing commission; suspension or revocation of license (Box 27, Folder 22)
- SB 603 (00) National criminal background check; child care providers (Box 27, Folder 23)
- SB 606 (00) Standards of learning (Box 27, Folder 24)
- SB 611 (00) Comprehensive services for at-risk youth and families (Box 27, Folder 25)
- SB 612 (00) Workforce development training fund (Box 27, Folder 26)
- SB 617 (00) Local telecommunications services (Box 27, Folder 27)
- SB 619 (00) DNA data bank (Box 27, Folder 28)
- SB 620 (00) Consumer real estate settlement protection act (Box 27, Folder 29)
- SB 626 (00) Procurement act; thresholds for small purchases and contracts (Box 29, Folder 30)
- SB 627 (00) Procurement act; procurement of architect or professional engineer services (Box 27, Folder 31)
- SB 628 (00) Economic and employment improvement program for disadvantaged (Box 27, Folder 32)
- SB 630 (00) Teaching scholarship loan program (Box 27, Folder 33)
- SB 631 (00) College scholarship assistance act (Box 27, Folder 34)
- SB 634 (00) State income tax check-off; removal of sunset (Box 27, Folder 35)
- SB 638 (00) Procurement act; declaration of purpose (Box 27, Folder 36)
- SB 639 (00) Procurement act; definitions; best value (Box 27, Folder 37)
- SB 643 (00) Zoning; regulation of mountain ridge construction (Box 27, Folder 38)
- SB 645 (00) Water quality monitoring and reporting (Box 27, Folder 39)
- SB 648 (00) Wetlands (Box 27, Folder 40)
- SB 649 (00) VASAP for reckless driving (Box 27, Folder 41)
- SB 652 (00) Virginia teaching scholarship loan program (Box 27, Folder 42)
- SB 653 (00) Illegal sales of cigarettes (Box 27, Folder 43)
- SB 654 (00) Gifted education consortium (Box 27, Folder 44)
- SB 656 (00) Portraits of member of the general assembly (Box 27, Folder 45)
- SB 660 (00) Handguns; purchase by former superintendent of state police (Box 27, Folder 46)
- SB 661 (00) Coalfield coalition authority (Box 27, Folder 47)
- SB 663 (00) Crime victim rights (Box 27, Folder 48)
- SB 664 (00) Income tax credits; forested buffers for waterways (Box 27, Folder 49)
- SB 665 (00) Rural health (Box 27, Folder 50)
- SB 666 (00) Propane education and research act; penalty (Box 27, Folder 51)
- SB 667 (00) Neighborhood assistance act; donations (Box 27, Folder 52)
- SB 668 (00) Soil and water conservation dams (Box 27, Folder 53)
- SB 670 (00) Location of state facilities and programs (Box 27, Folder 54)
- SB 672 (00) Legal holidays (Box 27, Folder 55)
- SB 673 (00) Advisory commission on schools for deaf and blind; per diem (Box 27, Folder 56)
- SB 674 (00) Milk and milk products; penalty (Box 27, Folder 57)
- SB 675 (00) School for the deaf and the blind at Hampton (Box 27, Folder 58)
- SB 676 (00) Uniform disposition of unclaimed property act (Box 27, Folder 59)
- SB 677 (00) Health care decisions (Box 27, Folder 60)
- SB 679 (00) Health professions; pharmacy (Box 27, Folder 61)
- SB 680 (00) Juror lists (Box 27, Folder 62)
- SB 681 (00) Liability for failure to provide adequate security or crowd control (Box 27, Folder 63)
- SB 682 (00) Indoor air quality task force (Box 27, Folder 64)
- SB 683 (00) Health professions; physicians assistants (Box 27, Folder 65)
- SB 685 (00) Adoption (Box 27, Folder 66)
- SB 688 (00) Special elections; vacancies in constitutional offices (Box 27, Folder 67)
- SB 689 (00) Chesapeake Bay Bridge and tunnel commission (Box 27, Folder 68)
- SB 691 (00) Records of founded complaints of child abuse and neglect (Box 27, Folder 69)
- SB 692 (00) Minimum standards for local jails (Box 27, Folder 70)
- SB 699 (00) Examinations of certain infant testing (Box 27, Folder 71)
- SB 706 (00) Advanced mathematics and technology diploma (Box 27, Folder 72)
- SB 708 (00) Temporary licensure of foreign licensed physicians (Box 27, Folder 73)
- SB 709 (00) Persons with mental retardation, developmental disabilities, etc. (Box 27, Folder 74)
- SB 711 (00) Housing revitalization zone act (Box 27, Folder 75)
- SB 713 (00) Upkeep and maintenance of Virginia War Memorial Carillon (Box 27, Folder 76)
- SB 715 (00) Resources authority (Box 27, Folder 77)
- SB 718 (00) Health insurance; provider panels (Box 27, Folder 78)
- SB 721 (00) Property owners' association act; records, liens, etc., study by HSC (Box 27, Folder 79)
- SB 722 (00) Condominium Act (Box 27, Folder 80)
- SB 725 (00) Testing children for elevated blood lead levels (Box 27, Folder 81)
- SB 730 (00) Absentee ballot applications (Box 27, Folder 82)
- SB 731 (00) Mental health, mental retardation and substance abuse services trust fund (Box 27, Folder 83)
- SB 732 (00) Department of employee relations counselors; grievance procedure (Box 27, Folder 84)
- SB 734 (00) Health care decisions act (Box 27, Folder 85)
- SB 735 (00) Workers' compensation; professional employer organizations (Box 27, Folder 86)
- SB 737 (00) Teaching scholarship loan program (Box 27, Folder 87)
- SB 739 (00) Maritime incident response advisory committee (Box 27, Folder 88)
- SB 750 (00) Free fishing days (Box 27, Folder 89)
- SB 751 (00) Transportation of persons less than 16 years old (Box 27, Folder 90)
- SB 752 (00) Service charges for Virginia ports authority (VPA) facilities (Box 27, Folder 91)
- SB 755 (00) Political activities of firefighters, EMTs and law-enforcement officers (Box 27, Folder 92)
- SB 756 (00) Salvage vehicles; recovered stolen vehicles (Box 27, Folder 93)
- SB 757 (00) Termination of spousal support; cohabitation (Box 27, Folder 94)
- SB 759 (00) Accident and sickness insurance guaranty association; structured settlement annuities (Box 27, Folder 95)
- SB 769 (00) Annual mixed beverage amphitheater licenses (Box 27, Folder 96)
- SB 770 (00) Local hospital or health center commissions (Box 27, Folder 97)
- SB 771 (00) Farm winery licenses (Box 27, Folder 98)
- SB 773 (00) Primary schedule in 2000 (Box 27, Folder 99)
- SB 776 (00) Investment partnership act (Box 27, Folder 100)
- SB 777 (00) University of Virginia; endowment funds (Box 27, Folder 101)
- SB 778 (00) DMHMRSAS conveyance of property (Box 27, Folder 102)
- SB 779 (00) Unemployment compensation benefits (Box 27, Folder 103)
- SB 780 (00) Powers of the trustees of town of York (Box 27, Folder 104)
- HB 4 (00) Elections; form of ballots, political party names on ballots (Box 28, Folder 1)
- HB 5 (00) Guideline for determination of child support (Box 28, Folder 2)
- HB 7 (00) UCC; warehouseman's liens (Box 28, Folder 3)
- HB 8 (00) Code commission; responsible for repealing obsolete provisions (Box 28, Folder 4)
- HB 9 (00) Code commission; evaluation of unfunded laws (Box 28, Folder 5)
- HB 10 (00) Special license plates; various military and charitable organizations (Box 28, Folder 6)
- HB 12 (00) Early retirement for certain local government officials (Box 28, Folder 7)
- HB 14 (00) Retirement system; employee benefits of city or town (Box 28, Folder 8)
- HB 17 (00) City of Franklin Charter (Box 28, Folder 9)
- HB 19 (00) Driver's license; reinstatement (Box 28, Folder 10)
- HB 20 (00) School board salaries (Box 28, Folder 11)
- HB 21 (00) Birth-related neurological injury compensation act; notification of beneficiaries (Box 28, Folder 12)
- HB 26 (00) Meetings of Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia (Box 28, Folder 13)
- HB 27 (00) Special license plates; vets of Iwo Jima and special forces association (Box 28, Folder 14)
- HB 28 (00) Property tax exemption; various organizations (Box 28, Folder 15)
- HB 29 (00) Budget bill; amends appropriations act of 1999, chapter 935 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- HB 30 (00) Budget bill; makes appropriations for the 2000-2002 biennium (Box 28, Folder 17)
- HB 31 (00) Higher educational institutions bond act of 2000 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- HB 37 (00) Real estate tax; reports of income data (Box 28, Folder 19)
- HB 39 (00) Special license plates; NARFE members (Box 28, Folder 20)
- HB 40 (00) Claims; Thomas A. Garrett (Box 28, Folder 21)
- HB 44 (00) Insurance; investments by domestic insurers (Box 28, Folder 22)
- HB 47 (00) Maintenance and support for a spouse; effect of remarriage (Box 28, Folder 23)
- HB 48 (00) Oyster grounds (Box 28, Folder 24)
- `HB 51 (00) Transient occupancy tax; Stafford County and Gloucester County (Box 28, Folder 25)
- HB 53 (00) Teacher-student ratios at detention homes (Box 28, Folder 26)
- HB 54 (00) FOIA; electronic communication meetings (Box 28, Folder 27)
- HB 56 (00) License plates; certain covering prohibited (Box 28, Folder 28)
- HB 57 (00) Vehicle registration cards; disabled owners (Box 28, Folder 29)
- HB 59 (00) Virginia War Memorial Foundation; Board of Trustees (Box 28, Folder 30)
- HB 60 (00) Colvin Run Road; designated a scenic highway (Box 28, Folder 31)
- HB 62 (00) Claims; Christopher Dungan (Box 28, Folder 32)
- HB 69 (00) Our-of-service inspections in town of Herndon and Wythe County (Box 28, Folder 33)
- HB 70 (00) Income tax; voluntary contribution to family and children's trust fund (Box 28, Folder 34)
- HB 71 (00) Running for multiple offices; names on ballots (Box 28, Folder 35)
- HB 77 (00) Line of duty act; death benefits (Box 28, Folder 36)
- HB 78 (00) Unlawful communication with prisoner (Box 28, Folder 37)
- HB 79 (00) Retirement plan; certain employees of public school divisions (Box 28, Folder 38)
- HB 80 (00) Claims; George M. Murray (Box 28, Folder 39)
- HB 84 (00) Reports of disciplinary actions to the board of medicine (Box 28, Folder 40)
- HB 93 (00) Ballots and voting equipment (Box 28, Folder 41)
- HB 94 (00) Individual income tax withholding (Box 28, Folder 42)
- HB 95 (00) Youthful offenders (Box 28, Folder 43)
- HB 96 (00) City of Bristol charter (Box 28, Folder 44)
- HB 99 (00) Sales tax exemption; property of nuclear power plants (Box 28, Folder 45)
- HB 100 (00) Deer kill permits (Box 28, Folder 46)
- HB 101 (00) Recordation tax exemption in the City of Lynchburg (Box 28, Folder 47)
- HB 106 (00) Sales tax exemption; various educational, cultural, etc. organizations (Box 28, Folder 48)
- HB 118 (00) City of Petersburg Charter (Box 28, Folder 49)
- HB 119 (00) Individual income tax; subtraction for disability income (Box 28, Folder 50)
- HB 123 (00) Motor fuels tax; exemption for recreational pleasure boats and ships (Box 28, Folder 51)
- HB 126 (00) Special license plates; Virginia Federation of Women's Clubs (Box 28, Folder 52)
- HB 129 (00) Town of Blacksburg charter (Box 28, Folder 53)
- HB 132 (00) Deferred compensation plan for state employees; administrative fees (Box 28, Folder 54)
- HB 133 (00) Retirement system; limitation of board liability (Box 28, Folder 55)
- HB 134 (00) Health insurance credits for retired local officers (Box 28, Folder 56)
- HB 135 (00) Retirement system; includes law officers' retirement system (Box 28, Folder 57)
- HB 141 (00) Infected sexual battery (Box 28, Folder 58)
- HB 142 (00) City of Norfolk charter (Box 28, Folder 59)
- HB 143 (00) Health insurance for faculty employees (Box 28, Folder 60)
- HB 144 (00) City of Lexington Charter (Box 28, Folder 61)
- HB 160 (00) Income tax; earned income tax credit for low-income families (Box 28, Folder 62)
- HB 164 (00) Motor vehicles; speed determination by plane or helicopter (Box 28, Folder 63)
- HB 165 (00) Health insurance; coverage for dental procedures (Box 28, Folder 64)
- HB 169 (00) Sexual battery (Box 28, Folder 65)
- HB 176 (00) Income tax; subtractions for income received by tobacco farmers (Box 28, Folder 66)
- HB 183 (00) Awards service handgun to widow of Troy D. Ashe (Box 28, Folder 67)
- HB 188 (00) Alternative education (Box 28, Folder 68)
- HB 190 (00) Taxation on intangible personal property; commercial fishing (Box 28, Folder 69)
- HB 198 (00) Use of explosives; issuance of permits, DMME to study (Box 28, Folder 70)
- HB 202 (00) Community corrections act for local-responsible offenders (Box 28, Folder 71)
- HB 203 (00) Standards of quality; educational technology (Box 28, Folder 72)
- HB 206 (00) Town of New Castle Charter (Box 28, Folder 73)
- HB 209 (00) Town of Pulaski Charter (Box 28, Folder 74)
- HB 211 (00) Town of Rocky Mount Charter (Box 28, Folder 75)
- HB 215 (00) Technology trust fund; parcel identification number, land record cover sheets (Box 28, Folder 76)
- HB 229 (00) Claims; Kathy Irene Farrell (Box 28, Folder 77)
- HB 234 (00) Town of Orange charter (Box 28, Folder 78)
- HB 235 (00) Claims; Deborah P. Tiller (Box 28, Folder 79)
- HB 236 (00) Industrial development authorities (Box 28, Folder 80)
- HB 238 (00) Town of Louisa Charter (Box 28, Folder 81)
- HB 245 (00) Standards of quality; elementary school guidance counselors (Box 28, Folder 82)
- HB 253 (00) Health professions; Board of Counseling (Box 28, Folder 83)
- HB 254 (00) Reports of bomb threats to law-enforcement and school authorities (Box 28, Folder 84)
- HB 255 (00) Food and beverages/meals tax; changes in food definition, study (Box 28, Folder 85)
- HB 259 (00) Town of Purcellville charter (Box 28, Folder 86)
- HB 261 (00) Special license plates; local government attorneys (Box 28, Folder 87)
- HB 262 (00) Liens for water and sewer charges (Box 28, Folder 88)